This is a photograph of our village.
这是我们村庄的一张照片.
Our village is in a valley.
我们的村庄坐落在一个山谷之中.
It is between two hills.
它位于两座小山之间.
The village is on a river.
它靠近一条小河.
Here is another photograph of the village.
这是我们村庄的另一张照片.
My wife and I are walking along the banks of the river.
我和妻子正沿河岸走着.
We are on the left.
我们在河的左侧.
There is a boy in the water.
河里面有个男孩.
He is swimming across the river.
他正横渡小河.
Here is another photograph.
这是另一张照片.
This is the school building.
这是学校大楼.
It is beside a park.
它位于公园的旁边.
The park is on the right.
公园在右面.
Some children are coming out of the building.
一些孩子正从楼里出来.
Some of them are going into the park.
他们中有几个正走进公园.